Bert JW Regeer

Bert JW Regeer Tel: +1-973-342-4882 Email: bertjw@regeer.org

Profile

I am a highly motivated individual, who enjoys working with technology. My strongest point is UNIX/Linux server administration and programming for these platforms. I have extensive experience writing shell scripts to accomplish new tasks. As well as maintaining and working with open source software to do web serving, e-mail and databases. Also I have completed network security testing for a university. I am going to school for a degree in Software Engineering, and currently maintain a 3.0 GPA

I am from the Netherlands, and as such bring a unique perspective to any team. Having lived in and travelled to many countries I am very open to new cultures and ideas. I have resided in the US for the last 7 years, and during that time have met many people that I then ended up working with.

Skills

On anoting Systems	Coftmans	Language	Databassa
Operating Systems	Software	Languages	Databases
FreeBSD	Subversion (svn)	C++	MySQL
Linux	cvs	C	sqlite 3
Mac OS X	Apache	PHP	PostgreSQL
Windows XP	lighttpd	bash/sh	
Windows 2000	qmail	C#	
Windows 2003	vpopmail	Perl	
	tinydns	Java	
	BIND	JavaScript	
	Samba	XML	
	cPanel	XSLT	
	ezmlm	CSS	
	daemontools	Visual Basic	
	binc-imap	PBASIC	
	pf (Firewall)	SX/B	
	pure-ftpd (pure-db)		
	VMWare Fusion		

Experience

System Administrator/Web Master; osnn.net - 2002 - current

- » Configure, maintain, secure and administrate FreeBSD and services
- » Tune server resources for the load
- » Migrating live website to new location
- » Monitoring of services for reliability and uptime (SSH, httpd, email)
- » Securing and threat assessment
- » Basic web-master duties/forum moderation

System Administrator; netuse.co.uk - August 2006 - current

- » Configure, maintain, secure and administrate FreeBSD and services
- » Monitoring of services for reliability and uptime (SSH, httpd, email)
- » Shell scripting to backup user data and e-mail
- » 24/7 stand-by, on-call administration
- » Using FreeBSD as a server platform has achieved greater uptime and availability

Volunteer worker; Blackhat - August 2008

- » Lay network and power cables for the students in the classes
- » Set up wireless nodes for Aruba networks
- » Direct people to and from lunch and check tickets
- » Sell T-Shirts and other Blackhat swag
- » Stuff swag bags

Security Audit; University of Advancing Technology - February 2007 - April 2007

- » General network security audit
- » Finding exploits in intranet web applications (SQL Injections)
- » Pen testing
- » Analyses of network protocols

VPS to server migration; netuse.co.uk - April 2006 - July, 2006

- » Migrated from virtual solution to dedicated server
- » Sendmail to qmail/vpopmail
- » Implement virtual user system with Pure-FTPD and pure-db
- » Shell scripts to maintain users/passwords for virtual users system
- » Migration of all user data with minimal downtime

System Administrator; Custom-Bytes Inc - 2004 - 2006

- » On-call system administration
- » CentOS running WHM/cPanel
- » Firewall maintenance
- » General help with services (BIND, Apache, Exim)

System Administrator; spammers-paradise.com - 2003 - 2006

- » Configure, maintain, secure and administrate FreeBSD and services
- » Monitoring of services for reliability and uptime (SSH, httpd, email)
- » System security lock-down
- » Ownership of domain/forum was transferred to me in January of 2007

Projects

These are the projects I am currently involved in, or have been involved in.

Near Space

As a team of 15 students we developed a near space pay-load along with the various science experiments. With a GPS device TNC and a HAM radio on-board we were able to track the near space pay-load using APRS data that was being sent back. After retrieving the pay-load we were able to retrieve the science data along with the pictures that we had taken with a still camera.

Christmas Tree Hack

I worked together with a team of other students at my university to set up an embedded web server running on the parallax PINK system, to control the christmas tree remotely. The PINK talked to an BS2 stamp which in turn controlled a relay box that allowed us to individually turn certain sections of the tree on and off

Education

2006 - Current, University of Advancing Technology; Tempe, Arizona

Degree: Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering

Major: Programming/Network Security Expected Graduation Date: August 2009